<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<!DOCTYPE Archive SYSTEM "http://greenstone.org/dtd/Archive/1.0/Archive.dtd">
<Archive>
<Section>
  <Description>
    <Metadata name="gsdlsourcefilename">import\advbeat_small\marc\locbeatles50.marc</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="gsdldoctype">indexed_doc</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="Language">en</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="Encoding">iso_8859_1</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="Source">locbeatles50.marc</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="SourceFile">locbeatles50.marc</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="SourceSegment">49</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="Plugin">MARCPlugin</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="dc.Format">MARC</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="FileFormat">MARC</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="dc.Title">Yesterday &amp;#091;sound recording&amp;#093; : the wonderful music of the Beatles.</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="dc.Publisher">New York, N.Y. :</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="dc.Publisher">Columbia House,</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="dc.Date">p1972.</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="dc.Description">Brief record.</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="dc.Description">Michelle -- A hard day's night -- If I fell -- All my loving -- Can't buy me love -- Eleanor Rigby -- I call your name -- Lucy in the sky with diamonds -- Yellow submarine -- Good day sunshine -- Love -- What is life? -- My sweet Lord -- Let it be -- Here, there and everywhere -- Ob la di-- ob la da -- Here comes the sun -- Mother nature's son -- Something -- You never give me your money -- Ticket to ride -- Norwegian wood -- Blackbird -- She's leaving home -- We can work it out -- This boy -- Rocky Raccoon -- Bangla Desh -- Come together -- From me to you -- Get back -- She loves you -- Strawberry fields forever -- Imagine -- You're gonna lose that girl -- When I'm 64 -- Help -- Tell me why -- A day in the life -- Lovely Linda -- The fool on the hill -- All you need is love -- Long and winding road -- Paperback writer -- Lady Madonna -- Carry that weight -- I will -- It don't come easy -- Maybe I'm amazed -- Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Heart's Club Band -- With a little help from my friends -- Hey Jude -- And I love her -- Penny Lane -- Uncle Albert -- Day tripper -- Magical mystery tour -- You've got to hide your love away -- Yesterday -- Hello, goodbye.</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="dc.Description">Performed by the Terry Baxter Orchestra and Chorus.</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="dc.Subject">Orchestral music, Arranged.</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="dc.Subject">Popular music 1971-1980.</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="dc.Creator">Terry Baxter Orchestra and Chorus. prf</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="dc.Creator">Beatles.</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="Identifier">HASH7c575f57a57cfb45ab0033s49</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="lastmodified">1652351099</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="lastmodifieddate">20220512</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="oailastmodified">1652361755</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="oailastmodifieddate">20220512</Metadata>
    <Metadata name="assocfilepath">HASH7c57/5f57a57c/fb45ab00/33s49.dir</Metadata>
  </Description>
  <Content>&lt;pre&gt;
 LDR 02433njm  22003737a 4500
001     5673930
005     19930324081815.9
007     sdubsmennmplu
008     930318s1972    nyuuun              eng  
035    _9 (DLC)   93706173
906    _a 7
       _b cbc
       _c orignew
       _d 5
       _e ncip
       _f 19
       _g y-genmusic
010    _a    93706173 
028 00 _a P6S 5748
       _b Columbia House
028 00 _a DS 937
       _b Columbia House
028 00 _a DS 938
       _b Columbia House
028 00 _a DS 939
       _b Columbia House
028 00 _a DS 940
       _b Columbia House
028 00 _a DS 941
       _b Columbia House
028 00 _a DS 942
       _b Columbia House
040    _a DLC
       _c DLC
050 00 _a Columbia House P6S 5748 (DS 937--DS 942)
245 00 _a Yesterday
       _h [sound recording] :
       _b the wonderful music of the Beatles.
260    _a New York, N.Y. :
       _b Columbia House,
       _c p1972.
300    _a 6 sound discs :
       _b analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo. ;
       _c 12 in.
440  2 _a A Columbia musical treasury
511 0  _a Performed by the Terry Baxter Orchestra and Chorus.
505 0  _a Michelle -- A hard day's night -- If I fell -- All my
 loving -- Can't buy me love -- Eleanor Rigby -- I call your
 name -- Lucy in the sky with diamonds -- Yellow submarine --
 Good day sunshine -- Love -- What is life? -- My sweet Lord --
 Let it be -- Here, there and everywhere -- Ob la di-- ob la da
 -- Here comes the sun -- Mother nature's son -- Something --
 You never give me your money -- Ticket to ride -- Norwegian
 wood -- Blackbird -- She's leaving home -- We can work it out
 -- This boy -- Rocky Raccoon -- Bangla Desh -- Come together --
 From me to you -- Get back -- She loves you -- Strawberry
 fields forever -- Imagine -- You're gonna lose that girl --
 When I'm 64 -- Help -- Tell me why -- A day in the life --
 Lovely Linda -- The fool on the hill -- All you need is love --
 Long and winding road -- Paperback writer -- Lady Madonna --
 Carry that weight -- I will -- It don't come easy -- Maybe I'm
 amazed -- Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Heart's Club Band -- With a
 little help from my friends -- Hey Jude -- And I love her --
 Penny Lane -- Uncle Albert -- Day tripper -- Magical mystery
 tour -- You've got to hide your love away -- Yesterday --
 Hello, goodbye.
500    _a Brief record.
650  0 _a Orchestral music, Arranged.
650  0 _a Popular music
       _y 1971-1980.
710 2  _a Terry Baxter Orchestra and Chorus.
       _4 prf
710 2  _a Beatles.
953    _a TA28
991    _b c-RecSound
       _h Columbia House P6S 5748 (DS 937--DS 942)
       _w MUSIC
&lt;/pre&gt;
</Content>
</Section>
</Archive>
